罗杰・唐纳森
电影
异         种
本・金斯利
迈克尔・麦德逊
阿尔弗雷德・莫利纳
福雷斯特・惠特克
以及
马格・海根伯格
韦帕・赫布利
米歇尔・威廉姆斯
特别介绍
娜塔莎・亨斯屈奇
三十年以来
强大的无线电
望远镜扫射天空
寻找异外文化的讯号
这个计划名为S.E.T.I.
就是探索地球之外的生命
美国政府实验室 犹他州达格韦市
氛化物毒气体
对不起
I'm sorry.
对不起？
I'm sorry?
她逃出来了
Sir, she's breaking out!
我们去找什么？
What are we looking for?
她跳过围栏！
She jumped over the fence!
她逃离时有两班火车．驶经这里
A couple of trains came through here about the time she escaped.
在那短时间内 她能走这么远？
Do you think she could have gotten this far in that time?
她有这么快吗？
Is she that fast?
她就是这么快
She is that fast.
还有这个
And this too.
- 三元一角 - 三元一角？
- $3. 10. - Three dollars and ten cents?
- 你的零钱 - 谢谢
- Your change. - Thank you.
有什么可帮你吗？
Can I help you?
总共十七元九毛五
The total is $ 17.95.
你的卡
Here's your card.
你想买那些吗？
Are you gonna buy those?
旅途愉快
Have a nice trip.
是褐色斜纹的帆布袋 有见过吗？
It's brown tweed bag, like a duffel. Do you see it anywhere?
- 先生，不在这里  - 服务生说是放在手谁车上的
- Sir, it's not here. - The porter said he put it on the cart.
这就是手谁车 不过没有帆布袋
This is the cart. There's no bag here.
政府当局说 这是最大型的地震
Government authorities said it was the largest earthquake to strike...
他骑着油脂闪电
He's riding Greased Lightning.
那是金凯德
That was Shorty Kincaid.
请享受风景
Enjoy the view.
不好意思
Excuse me.
我们不应给别人看到
We shouldn't be seen together.
父亲死去不久 你认为阿伦会怀疑吗？
Father hasn't been dead long. Do you think Arlen suspects?
不，我们也不是 立刻在一起的
No. It's not too soon for us to be together.
请拿出车票
Tickets.
你独自旅行吗？
Are you traveling by yourself?
你十二岁？
You're 12?
有人在洛杉矶接你吗？
Someone meeting you in Los Angeles?
当你十一岁吧 那么你只须付半价
We'll say you're 11. Then you only pay half price.
是我们的小女孩做的？
Our little girl did this?
她不是小女孩
She's not a little girl.
伤口发现的DNA类别和组织 都证实是属于她的
DNA typing and material found in those wounds proves it was her.
她可到任何地方，芝加哥 拉斯维加斯、洛杉矶
She could be anywhere. Chicago, Las Vegas, Los Angeles, anywhere.
我们要截停火车
We should stop the trains.
铁路人员和警方查问时 我们怎么回答？
And have the railroad and police ask questions we can't answer?
我们会派人在这些路线上的 每个站守候
We'll put key personnel at every stop along these lines.
我要派一个队伍追踪她
I want a team to track her.
把她搜寻回来
Hunt her down.
- 早安，吉尔  - 你好
- Good morning, Jill. - Hello.
- 麻烦你照顾我的猫  - 我们会好好照顾他
- Thanks for taking care of my cat. - We'll take good care of him.
我很快就会回来
I won't be gone very long.
保重
Take care.
再见
Bye-bye.
你的工作还不顺利吗？
Are you still having problems with the people at work?
他们都说我…
They point their finger at me saying...
我是怪人，很古怪
I'm the weird one, I'm the strange one.
为什么？因为我有感觉？
Why? Because I have feelings?
因我有感应？
Because I feel?
门外有人
There's someone at the door.
我不打算应门 任何人也可以稍后再来
I won't answer that. Whoever it is can come back at the end of the hour.
是找我的
That's for me.
抱歉打扰你们 我们需要你帮忙
Sorry to interrupt. We need your help, Dan.
我知道
I know.
我得先离开了
Gotta go.
菲奇先生稍后就会来
Mr. Fitch will be with you all in just a moment.
是了…
Well...
似乎我们都是为了 相同原因而来
I guess we all must be here for the same reason...
不论那是什么原因
whatever that is.
我是丹史密森
I'm Dan Smithson...
我也不知道我为何会来
and I don't know why I'm here either.
不过他们说需要我，而且这是 重要事情，所以我才来
But they said they needed me and it was important, so I came.
你做什么工作的？
What do you do, Dan?
我是心灵感应者
I'm an empath.
有时他让我看别人做的可怕事情
Sometimes they show me awful things people have done.
我尝试告诉他们为何会这样做
I try to tell them why they did it.
你有什么资格这样做？
What qualifies you for that?
我对事物有深切感受 就是这样
I feel things deeply, that's all.
我现在有什么感受？
What am I feeling now?
你相信没什么会影响你
You wanna believe that nothing affects you...
你什么也不怕
that you're not afraid of anything.
不过你很好奇
But you're curious...
就像我们所有人一样
just like the rest of us.
史蒂文阿登，哈佛人类学系
Stephen Arden. Harvard Anthropology Department.
专门研究跨文化行为
Expert at cross-cultural behavior.
罗拉贝克，分子生物学家
Laura Baker. Hi. Molecular biologist.
你呢？你做什么的？
And who are you, and what do you do?
普雷斯顿伦诺斯
Preston Lennox.
我来到这里
And if I'm here...
就证明有灾难发生
the shit has hit the fan.
伦诺斯先生 你的专长在哪一方面？
What exactly is your area of specialty, Mr. Lennox?
偶尔会为政府解决问题
I'm a freelance solution to our government's problems.
会是什么问题？
What exactly might they be?
一些别人不爱提及的问题
The kind people don't usually like to talk about.
你追捕别人，是吧？
You hunt people, don't you?
可以这样说
I guess so.
你在吗？时候不早了 还看电视
You in here? It's a little late for Tv.
你在吗？
You in here, honey?
晚安，我是萨维尔菲奇
Good evening, I'm Xavier Fitch.
这次行动由我负责
I'm in charge of this operation.
坐靠近一点可以吗？
Would you sit a little closer, please?
1974年11月
In November of 1974...
S.E.T.I.的一个小组…
a small group from S.E.T. I...
S.E.T.I.就是 探索地球之外的生命计划
S- E-T-I, Search for Extraterrestrial Intelligence...
利用阿雷西沃的无线电天线
used radio dishes at Arecibo
向所有人发放一个讯息
to send a message to whoever was listening.
他们发放了250位元的讯息
They sent a quarter of a kilobyte...
包括人类DNA的构造
including structure of human DNA...
我们太阳系的图表
a map of our solar system...
地球人口等有帮助的事实
population of the Earth. Helpful facts like that.
1993年1月 阿雷西沃接收到一个讯息
In January of 1993, Arecibo received a message back...
由外太空传送来的…
from an extra terrestrial...
但来历不明
unknown source.
真酷
That's great.
地球以外的智慧生物？
Intelligent life beyond this planet?
对
Yes.
讯息有两个
There were two communications.
第一个讯息促使 我们发现到甲烷
The first message turned out to be a superior catalyst for methane.
我们现在有潜能…
We now have the potential...
从这燃料制造无限的能源
to produce infinite energy from this clean-burning fuel.
这使我们相信 他们是友善的生物
This convinced us we were dealing with a friendly intelligence.
第二个讯息 是一个DNA的新排列
The second message turned out to be a new sequence of DNA...
并友善的指示 怎么与我们的DNA结合
with friendly instructions on how to combine it with ours.
那是技术上的数据 该由贝克博士解说
Here's some technical data. Get feedback from Dr. Baker.
基本上
Basically...
新组合的DNA排列次序
the new combined DNA sequence...
被注进一百个…
was injected into 100...
人类的卵细胞中
human ova.
有七个…
We got 7...
产生分裂
to divide.
四个逐渐停止了
Four petered out.
两个储在液体氮气中
Two were stored in liquid nitrogen.
我们让一个成长
And we allowed one to grow.
它的代号是西尔
Its code name is "Sil."
这是两小时后的形态
That's after 2 hours.
- 天
One day.
两天
Two days.
- 天啊  - 这成长过程真惊人
- My God. - This growth is amazing.
- 星期
A week.
- 是女孩子  - 对
- It's a girl. - Yes.
我们制造一个雌性 那么她就较温驯
We decided to make it female so it would be more docile...
- 和较易控制  - 温驯和容易受控？
and controllable. - More docile and controllable, huh?
你们消息真不灵通
Well, I guess you guys don't get out much.
这是她出生后一个月的状态
That's her 1 month after she was born.
你把她关在那儿？
So you kept her caged in there?
隔离她比较安全
It was safer to keep her isolated.
她不喜欢这样
She didn't like being locked up.
她不喜欢独自一人
She didn't like being alone.
是吗？
Didn't she?
她在隐藏身体里的一些东西
She's hiding something. Something inside.
说得没错
You're right, Dan.
这是她三个月大的情形 留心看
This is three months after she was born. Watch carefully.
那是什么？
What the hell was that?
把录影带转回
Back the tape up.
看她双眼
Watch her eyes.
眼睛急速跳动，她在做梦
Rapid eye movement. She's dreaming.
- 可怕的噩梦  - 是焦虑造成的反应
- She's having horrible nightmares. - It's some kind of anxiety reaction.
我也感到忧虑
Got me a little anxious.
也使研究队伍有点担忧
It made the research team a little anxious too...
所以我们决定中止实验
so the decision was made to terminate the experiment...
转而研究我们要应付什么
to run more research to see what we were dealing with.
你们打算毒死她？
You were going to gas her?
那就是我们的决定
That was the decision.
那使你很难受
It makes you feel mad.
要杀死她你很难过，对吗？
You feel mad that you had to kill her, don't you?
我不知道
I don't know.
对
Yes.
昨天在盐湖城附近的 一辆火车内发现一具尸体
Yesterday the body of a transient was found in a boxcar near Salt Lake City.
初步DNA测试所得的结论是
Preliminary DNA tests conclude...
他是被我们的西尔所杀的
he was killed by our creation, by our Sil.
发现到其他尸体吗？
Found any other bodies?
- 还没  - 晚一点就会
- Not yet. - You will.
她是个掠食者
She's a predator.
她双眼在前面
Her eyes are in front...
她能够判断跟猎物的距离
so she can judge the distance to her prey.
对
That's right.
你从哪里学会的？
Where'd you learn that?
探索频道播放的节目
I saw it on the Discovery Channel.
我也有看那节目
I caught that show myself.
- 伦诺斯先生  - 什么事？
- Mr. Lennox. - Yeah?
我们…
As the...
都不是科学家 你们明白在发生什么事吗？
non-scientist amongst us, are you clear about what's going on?
明白
I think so.
你得到外太空的一个程式
You created a monster...
以此制造了一个怪物
with a formula you got from outer space.
她逃走了 你想我们追寻和杀死她
The damn thing got away. Now you want us to hunt it down and kill it.
对不对？
Now, is that pretty close?
可以这样说
I guess.
你不想我们
You don't want us...
活捉她和研究她吗？
to capture her alive so that we can study her?
这是一次纯寻找 和纯消灭的行动
Laura, I think this is strictly a search and destroy operation.
向我求助的人 都想消灭他们的目标
Nobody ever asked me to find anything they didn't want dead.
我为你难过
I'm sorry for you.
是啊
Yeah, well...
谢谢你
Thank you, Dan.
我替她难过
I'm sorry for her.
请注意
May I have your attention, please?
欢迎到洛杉矶来 这是沙漠之星的终站
Welcome to Los Angeles. This is the terminal stop for the Desert Star.
请所有乘客离开
All passengers please disembark.
洛杉矶
有坏事发生了
Something bad happened here.
- 天啊 - 她的喉给压碎了
- No shit. - Crushed her larynx.
她很怕
She was afraid.
她害怕、惊慌
She's scared, frightened.
还很饿，她吃了很多
Hungry too. She's been eating like a horse.
她显然不是在节食
Our girl is definitely not on a diet.
她要提早储存能量
She's storing calories for something.
有头绪吗？
Any ideas?
我的天
Oh, my...
那是…
Well, that's...
看起来像是…
That looks like some sort of...
蛹，像是茧
chrysalis. Some kind of cocoon.
我们在寻找一只巨型飞峨吗？
What are we looking for, a giant moth?
若那是茧...
If that is a cocoon...
她现在一定已完全成长
She'll be fully-grown now. - Fully-grown.
或许她因此而未被我们发现
Maybe that's how she got by our people.
他们只在寻找一个孩子
They were looking for a child.
她的确是孩子
She is a child.
这儿很臭，我出去了
It stinks in here. I'm going outside.
向列车长取身分证 和信用卡号码
Get the conductors' ID and credit card numbers on your computer.
列车内没有它们影踪
There's no sign of them on the train.
- 她可能带走了他们 - 交给我办
- Let's assume she took them. - I'll see to that.
她感到受威胁时就会杀人
She kills if she's threatened.
而她是绝无悔意的
And she has no remorse about it. None.
洛杉矶绝对适合她
Of course, Los Angeles is perfect for her.
这是一个未来的城市
It's a city of the future.
什么事都有可能
Anything goes.
人口流动性强 大家都是陌生人
Totally mobile population. Everyone's a stranger.
无论她做什么
Very little is taboo or unacceptable.
都不会有人察觉
Whatever she does, no one will notice her.
随你怎说 所以…
Well, whatever. So...
洛杉矶将是我们作战的地方
Los Angeles is where the battle will be fought...
我们要胜利
...and won.
你看起来好漂亮
You look very pretty.
有一百块的吗？
Do you have a hundred?
在这
Here we are.
小心你的钱 很多人不会像我一样老实
Be more careful with your money. Not everybody's as honest as me.
你从外地来的？
Are you foreign?
会说英语吗？
Do you speak English?
- 会 - 拿着
- Yes. - Here. You keep this.
让我替你拿下来
Here, let me take this.
小心
Be careful here.
我会
Yes.
小心
Watch your step.
我们的实验室 访客基地一号
Our laboratory, Visitor Base One...
...正在迁移到大学现在没用的 病毒研究实验室
...is being moved to some empty virus research labs at the university.
他们正在搬运仪器 八点就可以运作
They're moving our equipment now. It'll be operational by 8:00.
你们先进自己房间 十五分钟后会合
Check into your rooms. Everyone out front in 15 minutes. We'll go over.
我们将做什么？
What will we do?
处理从火车上得来的证据
Process the evidence from the train.
我们能用那生物的DNA 繁殖它吗？
Could we try growing this creature with its own DNA?
这次不结合我们的DNA 看看它的脆弱程度
We do a version without ours this time and investigate its vulnerabilities.
主意不错
That'd be good.
- 我也想知道 - 有道理
- Then I could know how it feels. - Makes sense.
这个人类生命形态可能是掩饰
This human life form could be a mask. Without the camouflage...
没错，至少可让我们知道 在对付什么东西
You're right. At least we'd know what we were dealing with.
萨哈拉汽车旅馆
刚有两个笨蛋跑掉，我有客人
A couple of bozos just ran out. I got a customer.
- 可以帮你吗？ - 我想要个房间
- Yes, young lady. Can I help you? - I want a room.
连税合共六十二元 刚好是蜜月套房的价钱
62, including tax. That'll just about cover the Honeymoon Suite.
你好，你经常来吗？
Hi. Come here often?
你的星座是什么？
What's your sign?
厌倦了褐色的头发？
Tired of brunette?
改变
Change.
改变你头发的颜色
Change the color of your hair.
头发色素
Color-Tress.
我放大倍数
I've increased the magnification.
当我刺破细胞 外来的DNA就会加进去
When I pierce the cell, the foreign DNA will be introduced.
岂此有理
Shit!
摄影机坏了
The camera's gone down.
不好意思
Excuse me.
你有另外一部吗？
Do you have a replacement camera?
有，不过替换需要些时间
We do, but it'll take time for the technician to replace it.
这种事经常在我实验室发生 很简单
No. This happens in my lab all the time. It's simple to replace it.
你会替换？
You saying you can do it?
当然，我需要人帮忙
Sure I can. I just need somebody to give me a hand.
技师不可以进去，是机密
I don't want technicians in there. This is classified.
我去
I'll do it.
- 够爽快，我喜欢 - 我就是这样的
- Man of action, I like that. - That's me.
请替我扭开那一边，好吗？
Can you get that one for me?
给我摄影机
Give me the camera.
有些不对劲
Something's... Something's wrong.
糟，已经开始了
Christ, It's started already.
- 把盖子盖上 - 什么？
- It's started. Get the top back on. - What?
把盖子盖上
Laura, Press, get the top back on.
给你
Here you go.
她已经把细胞注入了
She must have penetrated the cell.
- 他妈的 - 那是什么？
- Shit. - What was that?
他弄掉了螺钉
He dropped the bolt.
- 去找螺钉，盖上盖子 - 我正在试
- Find the bolt. Get the top on. - I'm looking, Fitch.
他们听不到吗？
Can they hear me in there?
你们快点…
Laura, Press...
- 盖上盖子，我就让你们出来 - 它去哪了？
...get the top on, then I'll let you out. - Where'd it go?
- 它从铁丝网掉下去了 - 你可提起它吗？
- It fell through the grate. - Can you lift it up?
- 移不动它 - 它不动
- It's not gonna move. - This isn't going anywhere.
- 提不起来 - 普雷斯顿…
- No, can't get it! - Press...
...找那螺钉！
...you gotta get the bolt!
- 我移不动那铁丝网，它被悍接了 - 天啊
- Can't get it. The floor's welded down. - Oh, my God.
天啊
Press. Oh, my God.
- 我从没见过像这样的东西 - 天啊
- I've never seen anything like this. - Holy shit.
不能让他们出来
I can't let them out.
- 看 - 快点
- Press, look. - Come on.
让我们出来！
Fitch, let us out of here!
开门！
Open the goddamn door!
- 我要知道那里面是什么东西！ - 开门
- Not until I know what's in there! - Open it now!
- 让他们出来 - 不行
- Let them out. - I can't!
- 开门 - 让我们出来
- Open up the fucking door! - Let us out!
- 告诉我它会停止生长的 - 不会，放他们出来！
- Tell me it'll stop growing, Dan. - It's not, let them out!
开门！
Open up the door!
普雷斯顿
Press, Press.
这是什么怪物？!
What the fuck is that?!
去另一扇门
Laura, get to the other door!
- 放她出来！ - 不可以！
- Let her out, Fitch! - I can't!
- 让她走！ - 不可以
- Let her out! - I can't!
- 去你的 - 让她出来
- You motherfucker! - Let her out!
- 你一定要让他们出来 - 我无法按住它
- You've gotta let them out! - I can't hold it in!
走！
Get out of the way!
我要烧掉它！
I'm gonna burn it! Out of the way!
- 这是什么东西？ - 两分钟后这房间就会被烧毁
- What is this thing? - In 2 minutes, I'm burning the room!
我必须这么做
I have to do it!
在两分钟内消灭它
You have two minutes to kill it.
截断煤气管，用它来喷火
Disconnect the gas line. Use it as a flamethrower.
小心
Laura, watch out!
- 哪儿？ - 在管子里！
- Where'd it go? - In the pipes!
- 开门！ - 住嘴！
- Open the door! - Shut up, Dan!
剩下一分钟
One minute remaining.
罗拉
Laura...
它不动了，我想我杀了它
It stopped moving. I think I killed it.
它死了！开门！
It's dead! Open the door!
让他们出来
It's dead, Fitch. Let them out.
糟，它还没死
Oh, God, it's not dead.
我们怎么办？
- Shit. - What'll we do?
还剩三十秒
30 seconds remaining.
- 时间不多了，快点 - 开门
- There's not much time. Let's go. - Open the door!
- 快让他们出来 - 不行
- Let them out. - I can't do that.
- 我要依循协议书 - 什么协议书？
- I have to follow protocol! - What protocol?!
做这个实验的规则
The protocols by which we're doing this!
你并没告诉他们
You didn't tell them that before they went in.
- 让他们出来 - 12 , 11 , 10…
- Fitch, let them out. - Twelve, 11, 10...
- 让他们出来！ - 我必须跟从协议书
- Fitch, let them out! - I must follow protocol.
让他们出来
Let them out, Fitch!
快出来
Go. Get out of there!
3 , 2 , 1
Three, two, one.
- 我没有选择  - 是的，当然
- I had no choice. - Yeah, sure.
协议书说若出了状况 就把房间烧毁！
The protocol is to burn the room if anything went wrong!
我可在哪儿找到一个男人？
Where's a good place to find a man?
附近有一家夜总会 那儿有许多男人
There's plenty of guys at the Id around the corner. It's a club.
你不会有问题找到男人的
You won't have trouble meeting somebody there.
谢谢你
Thank you.
很容易找到的 有人排队的地方便是了
You can't miss it. Look for the long line.
我需要你的信用卡
I need your credit card...
...以支付你房间杂费 长途电话费等等
...for room incidentals, long distance calls and so forth.
信用卡？让我刷刷
Credit card? Zip zap?
美国运通，诸如此类的？
American Express, Visa, MasterCard?
对了，谢谢
There you go. Thanks. All right.
谢谢
Thank you.
等一下！
Wait a minute!
你不会想让这个落在坏人手里
You don't want this falling into the wrong hands.
对
No.
克劳尔挥杆，被守门员档着
Here's Justin Crawl. It's through and it's covered by the goalie.
喂？
Yeah?
列车长的信用卡被发现在…
The conductor's credit card turned up...
...好莱坞旅馆，货车正等着
...in a Hollywood motel. The van's out front.
出发吧
Let's go.
你们两个
You two.
慢慢享受
Enjoy yourselves.
长腿姐姐，你被看中了 进去
You, legs. You're in. Go on.
你从哪里来的？
Where are you from?
- 我不是本地人  - 什么？
- I'm foreign. - You're what?
- 我不是本地人  - 真的？
- I'm foreign. - Really?
慢慢来
Easy, easy.
我要去派对，但没有男伴
I've got a party to go to and no one to take me.
我可当你的男伴
I'll take you.
- 你会？ - 是的
- You will? - Yeah.
好，我要去洗手间
Okay. I'm going to the little girls' room.
在这里等我
Wait right here.
我很快回来
I'll be right back.
我不会走
I'll be right here.
不论付出任何代价？
Whatever it takes, right?
爱情与打仗都是公平的
All's fair in love and war.
看不清楚
Can't see much on that.
把录影带带回实验室 增强清晰度
Get this tape to the lab. Enhance it.
看看会否看清楚点
See if we can get a better look.
她样子看起来不错
She looks nice.
你知道她去哪里吗？
Do you have any idea where she went?
- 我去找她  - 她想去找男人
- I'll find her. - She wanted to meet a man.
我提议她到附近一间夜总会
I suggested a club called the Id around the corner.
把录影带带回去
Get the tape.
我要去派对，但没有男伴
I've got a party to go to and no one to take me.
在哪儿了？
Where is this party?
不知道
I don't know.
哇,你不能在此停车！
Whoa, you can't park there!
退回去！
Back that out!
- 你不可以进去  - 发生什么事？!
- No, you can't go in there. - What's going on?!
- 这儿发生谋杀案  - 不准离开！没有人可以离开！
- There's been a murder! - No one leaves here! I mean, nobody!
这地方总是会有各种行动的
There's always some action in this part of town.
蓝眼睛、金发
Blue-eyed blonde.
黑色紧身裤、粉红色毛衣 五尺十寸高，她跟谁走的？
Black leggings, pink sweater, 5' 10" tall. Who'd she leave with?
金发美女跟男人走并非大新闻
Blonde leaves with a guy is hardly news around here.
说出最受欢迎的人 不要说出没出，急的人
Name the top attractions. No losers.
他会帮她逃走
Assume he's socially adept. He'll be helping her out.
他是好人，并非坏蛋
A friendly guy, not an asshole.
我在想着
I'm thinking.
- 罗比跟一个金发女子离开  - 就是他
- Robbie left with a blonde. - That's him.
是他
That's him.
让我带你参观这房子
Come on. Let me show you the rest of the house.
我在那里弄得满身臭汗
I'm still sweaty from that place.
太挤拥了
It's so crowded.
喜欢吗？
Like it?
喜欢
Yes.
我想淋浴
I feel like a shower.
你想吗？
You want one?
告诉你
Tell you what.
我现在去淋浴
I'm taking one.
如果你稍后也想…
You wanna take one later...
没有问题
No problem.
脱去衣服
Take off your clothes.
我想看一看
I want to see you.
好美
Very nice.
送我回去好吗？
Take me back.
你在说什么？
What are you talking about?
你知道为何我们要来这
You know why we came here.
我改变主意了
I've changed my mind.
你说不
All right. You said "no."
我听到了，过来
It's duly noted. Come here.
我想离开！
I wanna go!
太迟了，你休想离开！
Too late. You're not leaving! You're not!
- 好吧  - 这才像样
- All right. - That's better.
什么回事？在夜总会杀掉女子 又杀掉这家伙
What's happening? Kills a girl at the club, kills this guy.
她像是精神病患者
I'd say she fits the definition of a psychopath.
没什么会抑制她
Nothing inhibits her.
没道德观念，没社会结构
No moral sense, no social structure.
她并非沉溺在母爱之中
She wasn't exactly smothered with a mother's love or taught good manners.
究竟发生了什么事
I asked what was happening.
他做了一些事使她生气
He did something, she was angry.
若她感到受威胁或有人阻碍她 她就会杀死对方
She'll kill if she's threatened or if anyone gets in her way.
阻碍她什么？
Of what?
她的生命周期
Her life cycle.
她似乎想交配
I think she's trying to mate.
进行繁殖
Reproduce.
好
Okay.
为何她要杀那女子？
So why did she kill the girl?
性竞争
Sexual competition.
她不会在竞争上屈服
She's hard on the competition.
她想交配
Now she managed to mate.
似乎不成功，他仍穿着裤子
Doesn't look like a success. He's still got his pants on.
- 她很沮丧  - 谁不会？
- She's frustrated. - Who isn't?
她有什么问题？是她跟他来的
What's her problem? She was here with him.
或许她拒绝他
Maybe she rejected him.
她大概有特别感官
She probably has special senses.
老鼠能够感应配偶 是否有病或基因不健全的
Rats can sense diseased or genetic damage in their potential mates...
...所以我们可以测试他
...so we can test his body...
...检查他有没有遗传病或缺憾 让他不能做她的...
...for hereditary diseases or defects that would make him a loser...
...配偶
...essentially.
是注射针
Needles.
也许他是瘾君子 或是糖尿病人
Maybe he was a doper, or a diabetic.
两者都不能够接受 对不起
Either way would make him unacceptable. Excuse me.
是了
All right.
胰岛素，他是糖尿病患者
Insulin. Diabetic. There you have it.
她可以离开的 为何要杀死他？
She could have just walked out. Why kill him?
他让她生气
He pissed her off.
有些家伙被拒绝了 也死缠烂打的
Some men, when rejected, get insistent.
- 追踪他的汽车  - 已发了通报
- Put an APB out on his car. - We have.
我们要返回旅馆 我要查个水落石出
We'll go back to the motel. I want to check it out.
还说比较温驯和易受控制？
More docile and controllable, huh, Fitch?
- 你认为怎样？ - 我认为怎样？
- What do you think, Dan? - What do I think?
我想她现在想独自一人
I think she'd want to be alone now.
这么多辆车停在外面 她是不会来的
She won't come here with all these cars outside.
你指她自有方法回来？
You're assuming she could find her way back here.
有可能
She could.
这是什么？
What is it?
也许是经血
Maybe menstrual blood.
如果她有经期 即是她可以繁殖
If she's menstruating, she can reproduce.
对，我知道
Yes, I know.
糟糕
Shit.
天
Oh, Jesus.
请让开
Excuse me.
快叫救护车来 谁人有电话？
Call a paramedic! Anybody got a phone?
十号公路向西行的交通
If your commute takes you westbound on the 10 freeway...
...将有一小时的延误
...expect an hour delay.
往．马里布的车程将会缓慢
The drive will be slow to Malibu.
只限无铅汽油
录影带的清晰度仍不理想
The video enhancement is not that great.
你猜她多大？ 二十岁？二十三岁？
How old do you think she is? Twenty, 23?
她的生殖系统应该完全成熟
Her reproductive system should be fully developed.
她的生理时钟必定很亢奋
Her biological clock must be in hyperdrive.
她想要孩子
She wants a baby.
若她有孩子，我们就有麻烦
If she has a child our problems have just begun.
若她怀着的是个男孩 而他的成长速度如西尔一样
If her offspring is male and develops at the same rate as Sil...
...六个月后就有能力繁殖了
...it could reproduce in 6 months.
天晓得他能使多少个女性怀孕
God knows how many females it could impregnate.
菲奇
Fitch.
当一个掠食性品种来到
When a predatory species is introduced...
...一个封闭的生态系统
...into a closed ecological system...
...较弱的品种就会灭绝
...the extinction of the weaker species is inevitable.
他们在圣莫尼卡 找到已没汽油的宝．马
They found the murdered guy's BMW, out of gas in Santa Monica.
她叫什么名字？
What's her name?
- 我不知道  - 你是谁？
- I don't know. - Who are you?
她没有身分证 我想确定她没大碍
She didn't have any ID. I thought I'd make sure she was okay.
她有医疗保险吗？
You think she's got insurance?
我不知道 算在我信用卡的帐上吧
I don't know. Just put it on my credit card for now.
但你连她的名字也不知道 像你这样的人真难得
And you don't know her name. Guys like you are hard to find.
让实验室做个实验
Get a lab workup on that, stat.
给她照X光片，要照这里
Get her up to x-ray. I want an x-ray on this.
看似是肩胛骨碎裂
It looks like a scapula fracture.
你的肩膀
Your shoulder wound.
怎会这样的？
What's going on here?
医生，我们现在需要你.一个孩子烧伤刚进来
Doctor, we need you now. A child burn victim just came in.
- 这是怎么回事？ - 请医生
- What is going on here? - Doctor, please.
天！你看到她的肩膀吗？
Jesus Christ! Did you see her shoulder?
请你立刻过去
Please. We need you immediately.
你没事
You're okay.
我没事
I'm okay.
但你受了重伤的
I was sure you were seriously injured.
我没事
I'm okay.
这真是奇迹
You are. It's a miracle.
可以离开了吗？
Can we go?
医生说你可以离开吗？
Did the doctor say you could go?
是
Yes.
我们会派人到那边
We'll send somebody over there. Thanks a lot.
帕克湾医院的医生 说有怪事发生
Doctor over at Parkbay Hospital called in with some weird story.
查查看，只在数英里外
We should check it out. It's a few miles away.
罗拉
Laura...
...普雷斯顿，查探一下
...Press, take a car, check it out.
- 帕克湾医院？ - 对，帕克湾
- Parkbay Hospital?  - Yeah, Parkbay.
她用走的
She walked.
她沿着那边走…
She walked that way...
...就在不久之前
...not too long ago.
吃些水果和起司吧
Got some fruit and cheese.
那是什么？
What is that?
你指那热水池？
You mean the hot tub?
热水池
A hot tub.
我爱这个地方
I love this place.
远离车辆、人和事
It's away from the traffic and business and people.
有时觉得自己并不在洛杉矶
Sometimes it feels like you're not in L.A. Anymore.
过来
Here.
我们要永远留住这一刻
We'll immortalize the moment.
看着摄影机
Look at the camera.
- 她的骨骼重生了 - 是她
- This girl literally reformed her bones. - It's her.
谁帮她挂号的？
Who checked her in?
然我们看看
I don't know. Let's find out.
她没有保险 所以他用信用卡帮她付了帐
She had no insurance so this guy put it on his own credit card.
是这个档案，他叫约翰凯瑞
Here's the file. John F. Carey.
有驾．驶执照或地址的资料吗？
You don't have a driver's license or home address?
没有 只有他的信用卡刷卡纪录
No, sir. Just an imprint of his credit card.
给我们印一张你有的资料
Give us a printout of what you've got.
没问题
No problem.
吃糖吗？
Some candy?
在帕利塞德 还有他的电话号码
It's in the Palisades and he's got a phone number.
告诉菲奇我们的目的地 试着打电话给约翰凯瑞
Tell Fitch where we're headed, and try to get John Carey on the line.
让我去接
I'd better get the phone.
答录机响了，应该留话吗？
I've got his machine. Should I leave a message?
好
Yeah.
告诉他他将要跟 外太空生物交配
Tell him he's about to copulate with a creature from outer space.
- 交配？ - 对
- Copulate, huh? - Yeah.
我喜欢你
I like you.
我知道
I know.
我们在一起也不会太快
It's not too soon for us to be together.
对，不会太快
No, it's not too soon.
你不用穿裤子
You don't need these.
你太急了
Hey, hey. That's a little fast.
怎么了？
What's the matter?
慢慢来
Take it easy.
放松点
Just relax.
还有许多时间
There's plenty of time.
什么事？
What is it?
有人在门外
I think someone's at the door.
别走
Don't go.
求求你 我想要孩子
Please. I want a baby.
什么？! 对不起？
What?! Excuse me?
从旁边去看看
Let's go around the side.
外面
Outside.
- 什么事？ - 是松鼠！该死的松鼠！
- What happened?  - A squirrel! A fucking squirrel!
- 她曾在这儿 - 没错
- She was here. - Yeah, she was.
我想确定她离开了
I wanna make sure she's not still here.
应检查尸体 有没有曾性交过的迹象
Perhaps we should check the body for evidence that they've had sex.
血淋淋的情景叫我害怕
I used to be scared at the sight of blood.
我已习惯了
Now I guess I'm getting used to it.
对啊
Oh, yes.
- 救我！ - 什么事？
- Help me, please! - Oh, my God. What's the matter?
我们在客厅发现的
We found this in the living room.
她喜欢他
She liked him.
不够清楚
Well, not enough.
跟录像监测所拍出来的差不多
Can't see any more on that than we did on the video monitor.
他没有帮她拍到一张好相片
He didn't get a good picture of her.
水里没发现精液
There's no evidence of semen in the hot tub water.
也许她带走了
Maybe she took it with.
那么她没有交配
So she probably hasn't managed to mate.
- 我们打扰了她  - 是的，应该是
- We interrupted her. - Yes, I think we did.
给我些我可以用的
Give me something I can use.
你最近想到了什么？
What have you come up with lately, Fitch?
她不怕我们
She's not scared of us.
这是肯定的
That's for sure.
我们被难倒了
We're all beat.
先回旅馆休，急一下
We'll go back to the hotel and rest.
明晚
Tomorrow night...
...我们再回到夜总会
...we'll go back to the club.
- 进行监视  - 进行监视
- Stake it out. - Stake it out.
她并不蠢
She's not stupid.
她不会重蹈覆辙
She won't repeat herself.
没理由再去那里 那儿提供了个坏榜样
There's no point going there. It provided a poor specimen.
很难说
I'm not sure.
她只来了两天，只知道那地方
She's been in the city two days. It's what she knows.
我宁愿再到夜总会看看
I'd rather try the club...
..不要只坐在指挥中心 回忆着我们多接近成功
...than sit at the command center reminiscing about how close we got.
她可会是厉害的生物武器
She would make one excellent biological weapon.
若有人认为我们是 散布宇宙间的…
If someone thought we were some kind of galactic weed that would...
...银河系废物
...spread through the universe.
你的意思是...
So what you're saying is that...
...她是疗药，而我们是病源
...she's the cure and we're the disease.
说得好
That's well said.
罗拉贝克
"Baker, Laura.
加州锡米谷 米德大道1735号
1735 Meander Drive, Simi v alley, california."
是你吗？
That's you, right?
我上次查的资料是这样的
Last time I checked.
你在这做什么？
What do you do for kicks out there?
怀念像你这样的家伙
Pine for guys like you.
我正这样想
That's what I thought.
你们饿吗？
So anyone hungry?
不，我很疲倦，我想去休息
No, thanks. I'm beat. I'm gonna try to get some sleep.
- 晚安  - 晚安
- Good night. - Yeah. Night.
- 我可以跟你一起吃  - 谢了
- I'll have something to eat with you. - Thanks, Dan.
- 你做过噩梦吗？ - 做过
- Do you ever have nightmares? - Yes.
请松绑我的双手
Please untie my hands.
- 我不会伤害你的  - 我做了噩梦
- I wouldn't hurt you. Please. - I have them.
噩梦想告诉我我是谁
I think they tell me who I am.
你为何要这样做？
Why are you doing this to me?
我不知道为何我在这里
I don't know why I'm here.
我不知道我是谁，谁派我来
I don't know who I am, who sent me.
- 你知道吗？ - 不！
- Do you? - No!
- 你为何在此？ - 我不知道
- Why do you think you're here? - I don't know.
请放过我
Please let me go.
求求你，让我走
Please. Please, let me go.
我不会伤害你
I wouldn't hurt you.
我保证
I promise.
- 我不会伤害你的  - 你会的
- I wouldn't hurt you. - Yes, you would.
只是你还不知道
You just don't know it yet.
我不会！
No, I wouldn't!
求求你！
Please!
我双手很疼
My hands are hurting me.
谢谢你
Thank you.
我的天！
Oh, my God!
不！
Oh, my God, no!
天，不！
No! No!
危险，高电压
罗拉和普雷斯顿喜欢对方
Laura and Press, they like each other.
他们不流露自己的感受
They just don't like to show how they feel.
什么？
What?
罗拉和普雷斯顿 喜欢对方
Laura and Press, they like each other.
随你怎说吧，丹
Yeah, whatever you say, Dan.
这儿烟雾弥漫，我打算出去
Look, it's really smoky in here. I'm gonna go outside, get some air.
在货车上歇一歇 这简直是浪费时间
Think I'll lie down in the van. Have a rest. This is a complete waste of time.
感觉上像是在浪费时间吗？
Get a feeling you're on a wild goose chase?
对
Yeah.
请让开
Excuse me.
滚出去，这是我的地盘
Get out of here. This is my trashcan.
是你
It's you.
喂
Hey!
她在这儿
She's here! Hey!
-是她吗？ -是
- Dan. Is that her? - Yeah.
这儿
Here.
上车
Get in the van.
上车！
Everybody get in the van!
他们朝山区走 我们需要直升机
They're heading into the hills. We'll need the helicopters.
我们要上尼科斯峡谷 在茂贺兰拦截她
We're going up Nichols canyon. One of you try to block her at Mulholland.
小心
Watch it!
我的天！
Oh, my God!
已封锁道路 我们一定得告诉报界些消息
We blocked the road. We've gotta tell the press something.
随便你怎么告诉他们 但别说出事实
Tell them what you want, just don't tell them the truth.
我不认为她会在夜总会出现 那太简单了
I don't buy her showing up at the club. It's too damn convenient.
眼见为实 你不相信你双眼吗？
Seeing is believing or don't you trust your eyes?
回去！叫这些人统统回去！
Get back! Get all these people back!
有些不对
Fitch. Fitch. It doesn't feel right.
长官！
Sir!
我们在其中一道车门 发现一只断指
We found a severed thumb in one of the doors that got ripped off.
- 让我看看  - 她或许给夹在门中
- Let me see that. - She may have caught it in the door.
拿去实验室，看看是否属于她
Get to the lab, see if it's hers.
- 可从基因上辨别出来  - 这件事完了
- It'll be genetically identifiable. - It's all over, everyone.
明天你可重过自己的生活
Tomorrow you can go back to your lives.
恭喜你们，做得好
Congratulations on a job well done.
就这样结束了？
Just like that, huh, Fitch?
我不认为
I don't think so.
留话给我 法兰克，我会和你吃晚餮
Leave me a message. And Frank, I'm going to dinner.
我们在哪见面？再见
Where are we meeting? Bye, sweetie.
服务生
Waiter.
我猜我们赢了
Well, I guess we won.
- 我们赢了，科学输了  - 我不认为我们会这样赢
- We won, science lost. - I didn't think we'd get her this way.
- 没那么容易  - 你会怀念她吗？
- Not that easy. - You sound like you'll miss her.
会的
I guess I will.
我想我尊重她
I think I respected her.
这的确是不好做的工作 但我很高兴跟你们三人合作
I know this was a hellish job, but I really enjoyed working with you three.
既然国税局请客 让我们再多喝一杯
And since Uncle Sam is buying, let's have another round.
服务生！
Waiter!
我不喝酒的
I don't... I don't drink.
今晚你会的
Don't worry, Dan. Tonight you will.
想跳舞吗？
You wanna dance?
- 谁？我？ - 没错
- Who, me? - Yeah, you.
- 好  - 对啊
- All right. - Okay.
我知道你没家室 在纽约有女朋友吗？
I know you don't have a family. Do you have a girlfriend in New York?
曾经有几个，不过都不久
I guess I've had a few, but they don't hang around very long.
可能我有太多秘密
I guess I keep too many secrets.
跟我分享一个
You wanna share one with me?
- 现在？ - 对
- Right now? - Yeah.
我知道你是做什么的 吓不到我的
I know what you do, and it doesn't scare me.
- 真的？ - 真的
- Really? - No.
但却使许多人害怕
Well, it does most people.
我还要再见你
I wouldn't wanna never see you again.
- 喂  - 你在...?
- Hey. - What are you...?
对不起 我认错人
I'm sorry. I'm sorry. I thought you were somebody else.
对不起
I'm sorry.
没事吗？
You okay?
我以为是西尔 我见到一头金发
I thought it was Sil. I saw the blonde hair.
她死了
She's dead, Press.
拇指的化验，证明是她的
The tests on the thumb proved it was her.
你相信化验，而我则有胆识 我不相信
You got your test and I got my gut. I just don't buy it.
只要你还感到她存在 你都不会放弃
I think as long as you feel she's out there, you got a mission.
或者你不想结束这任务
Maybe you don't want this job to be over.
或者是，那又如何？
Well, maybe not. So what?
谢谢你那支舞
Thanks for the dance.
晚安
Good night.
这是什么？
What do you call this?
长岛冰茶
It's called a Long Island Ice Tea.
有茶的成分吗？
It's got tea in it?
没有
Nope.
很香，我可以试试吗？
Smells nice, can I try some?
请便
Help yourself.
这会迷倒你男朋友吗？
Does it work on your boyfriend?
令他厌恶
Yeah. As a repellent.
他这个年纪 身型还保持得很好
I don't know. I think he's in remarkably good shape for a man his age.
一杯长岛冰茶
One Long Island Ice Tea.
我喜欢这些茶
I like these cups of tea.
- 什么？ - 太好了
- What? - That's great.
嘿，给我一杯
Hey, give me one of those.
我喜欢这些茶
I like these cups of tea, man.
我很累，我要去睡了
You guys, I'm tired. I'm gonna go to bed.
那又怎样？
So?
她说要上床睡觉
She's going to bed.
没错
I guess.
但她仍然...
She still...
...想见你
...wants to see you though.
我去看看你的话是否正确
Maybe I'll go find out if you're right about that.
地震时我不想在这里
I'd hate to be in here during an earthquake.
没错
Yeah.
你到哪一层？
What floor do you want?
十楼，麻烦你
Ten, please.
我喜欢你的香水
I like your perfume.
是吗？
You do?
- 谢谢  - 对不起，我要出去
- Thank you. - Excuse me. I get out here.
晚安
Good night.
- 你好 - 你好
- Hi. - Hi.
请勿打扰
你想要什么吗？
Did you want something?
- 也许 - 也许？
- Maybe. - Maybe?
打扫房间
Housekeeping.
丹
Dan. Dan.
我猜那两个女子 会喜欢像我们这样不平凡的男人
Those two over there. Bet they like unusual men like us.
女人觉得我很奇怪
Women think I'm strange.
我有点不舒服
I don't feel well.
别说傻话
Don't be silly.
过去跟她们聊天
Just go over there and talk to them.
我要走了 我觉得你该跟我一起走，好吗？
I have to go. And I think you should leave with me, okay?
我想多留一会
I'm gonna stay for a while, actually.
好吧
Okay.
明天见
I'll see you tomorrow.
打扫房间
House keeping.
- 你好 - 你好
- Hi. - Hi.
我在那边坐着，我在猜…
I was sitting over there, wondering...
...这两位聪明漂亮的女子 怎么没有男伴
...what two intelligent, glamorous women were doing without dates.
我叫史蒂文阿登
My name's Stephen Arden.
在哈佛教授人类学的
I teach anthropology at Harvard.
- 我曾住在波士顿  - 是吗？
- I lived in Boston once. - Yeah?
一年
For a year.
- 冷得要命  - 的确很冷
- Froze my butt off. - It's cold in Boston.
他们是比尔和东尼 我忘了你的名字
This is Bill and Tony. I forget your name.
有趣的袜子
Cute little socks.
起来
Stand up.
你怎么能进来的？
How'd you get in here?
- 偷了钥匙  - 什么？
- I stole the key. - What?
我在楼下见到你
I saw you downstairs, but you were with all those people.
所以我就上来等你
So I thought I'd come up and wait.
这种事不经常发生在我身上
This kind of thing doesn't usually happen to me.
我想跟你一起
I just want to be with you.
太好了
Oh, yes.
不用做安全措施吗？
What about protection?
她在这儿
She's here. She's here.
普雷斯顿
Press?
有人在门外
Someone's at the door.
是谁？
Who's there?
普雷斯顿，罗拉
Press, Laura.
是丹，我有事告诉你
It's Dan. I gotta talk to you.
他到底想怎样？
Christ, what does he want?
- 什么事？ - 我有不祥预感
- What's the problem, Dan? - I just got this terrible feeling.
我奇怪地想到 西尔跟阿登一起的影像
I get this strange thought, this image of Sil with Arden.
西尔跟阿登
Sil's next door with Arden, Press.
不可能，她已死了
No, no, no. She's dead, Dan.
我经过他房间 听到里面有另外一人
I went to his room and there's someone in there with him.
- 你有敲门吗？ - 有，但我不知道她会做什么
- Did you knock on the door? - Yes, but I don't know what she'll do.
他们很吵，他们在做爱
They're making a lot of noise. They're having sex.
我知道是西尔
I know it's Sil, I know it!
好吧
Okay.
我相信你，我去穿衣
I believe you. I'll get dressed.
你使我欲仙欲死
I enjoyed that immensely.
- 我感觉到了 - 什么？
- I felt it. - What?
开始了
It's started.
什么？
What's started?
生命
Life.
你真可爱
Oh, my darling girl.
在某些文化里，女人相信 她们知道自己何时怀孕
In some cultures, women believe they know the moment of conception...
你不相信我？感觉一下
Don't you believe me? Feel.
天啊！
Holy shit!
希望你说得对
I hope you're right about this, Dan.
- 她朝地下室去了  - 我们走楼梯
- She's headed for the basement. - We'll take the stairs.
罗拉，跟我来！
Laura, come with me!
来！
Come on!
如果她怀孕了 我们必须在她生产前找到她
If she's pregnant, we gotta get to her before she gives birth.
我们不知道我们在跟什么周旋
God. We don't know what we're dealing with here.
她可以生一打孩子 甚至可产一千个卵
She could have a dozen babies. She could lay 1000 eggs!
有见到阿登吗？
Oh, God. Did you see Arden?
有，那个可怜的家伙
Yeah, I did, that poor bastard.
我们可以困住她 防火门在底层出口打开了
We can trap her. The fire door opens from the inside at the bottom exit.
然后怎样？
Then what?
他妈的
Holy shit.
- 哦，上帝  - 那婊子穿过了钢门
- Oh, my God. - The bitch went through a steel door!
菲奇！丹！我们在停车场！ 她溜掉了！
Fitch! Dan! We're in the garage! She got past us!
- 你见到她？ - 她在我们到达前已离开
- You saw her? - She was gone before we got here.
- 来  - 你见到她！
- Here. - You saw her!
- 看看那扇门！ - 她去哪儿了？
- Look at the door! - Which way did she go?
- 普雷斯顿呢？ - 到了隧道下面！
- Where's Press? - He took off down that tunnel.
她感到受威胁时就会杀人
She kills if she feels threatened. She kills if she feels threatened.
她一定曾经过这儿
She must've come through here.
她曾下来这里
She went down here. There's no other way.
对，她曾在这下面
Yeah, she's down there.
走吧
Let's go.
退后，我去清除一下
Stand back, I'll clear it out.
她朝哪个方向，丹？
Which way did she go, Dan?
- 我不知道  - 什么？
- I don't know. - What?
我不确定
I'm not sure. She's here.
想一想！你是有超感官的能力！ 那个方向？
Think. You're supposed to have some extrasensory power! Which way?
- 她去了哪个方向？ - 我不知道！
- Which way did she go, Dan? - I don't know! I don't know!
- 那边  - 这已经足够了
- I think she went that way. - That's good enough for me.
你认为她往那边走？
You think she went that way?
你什么也不知道的，不是吗？
You don't fucking know, don't you? You don't fucking know.
我往这边走，跟我来
I'll go this way. You come with me.
- 丹，跟我来！ - 菲奇
- Come with me, Dan! - Fitch.
我认为她往这边走了
I think she went this way.
丹？
Dan?
菲奇
Fitch. Fitch.
丹？
Dan?
怎么了？
What happened?
我可以感觉到她
I can feel her.
她在那一边
She's that way.
我从没想过要杀人的
I never thought I'd want to kill something.
我也没想过
Never thought I'd want to.
是这边 在这里后面
It's this way. It's back here.
她在里面
Hey, she went in here.
这是在地震时给震开的
This must have opened up during the earthquake.
你们退后
Okay, stand back.
是油吗？
Is that oil?
好像是
Looks like it.
我回去看看能否把她冲出来
I'm going back there to see if I can flush her out.
若她穿过这儿回来，便攻击她
If she comes back through here, let her have it.
丹
Dan. Dan!
- 那是什么？ - 我不知道
- Dan, what is it?  - I don't know.
不知道
I don't know.
丹
Dan.
没事
Okay.
没事的
It's okay.
没有人会伤害你
Nobody's gonna hurt you.
过来
You come here.
过来，我扶你
Come on. I got you.
丹出事了！
Press, something's happened to Dan!
没事吗？
You okay?
糟糕
Shit!
丹？
Dan?
我被困了！
I'm stuck!
帮帮我！我被困住了！
I need your help! I'm stuck!
丹，撑着点！
Dan, you gotta hang on!
普雷斯顿
Press!
撑着点，丹
Dan, keep on.
普雷斯顿
Press!
撑着点！
Hang on, Dan!
撑着点
Hang on!
我抓住你了
I got you.
I got you, Dan. Hang on.
糟糕
Shit.
撑着点
Hang on!
丹，撑着点
Hang on, Dan!
除掉她！
Get rid of her, Press!
低头
Duck your head.
去你的，死吧
Let go, you motherfucker.
- 我抓住你了  - 糟糕
- I got you. Hold on, I got you. - Shit.
我还以为会没命
I thought I was dead.
我以为你再没机会喝长岛冰茶了
I thought you'd drank your last Long Island Ice Tea.
我以为大家都是
Yeah, I thought we all had.
你没事吗？
Hey, you okay?
没事
Yeah, I'm okay.
我的裤子很邋遢
My pants are a little messed up.
不过我没事
But I'm okay.
她是半人半怪物
She was half us, half something else.
不知道哪边才是掠食性的
I wonder which was the predatory half.
那死了的一边
The dead half.
我们走吧
Let's get the hell out of here.
没想过回到水渠来 会这么开心的
I never thought I'd be so happy to be back in a sewer.
浮煊
谢谢观赏